(speaker) So here I am calculating the output.
现在我将计算输出
So like I said before, we're only
正如之前提到的
really concerned with the final output,
我们真正关心的是最终输出
which is what we're going to use to predict our sentiment.
我们将用输出来预测我们的情感
So we just need to grab the last one
我们需要获取最后一个输出
and we can do that using outputs.
可以使用 outputs() 进行获取
So this is saying, give us all the rows, so all the batches.
这个表示提供所有的行 所有批次
And this is saying, give us the last column.
这个表示提供最后一列
Remember that we're passing a bunch of reviews
我们同时传入一系列的影评
in at the same time because that's our batch,
因为这是我们的批次内容
and then the last column is just the last output from our LSTM
最后一列是 LSTM 单元的最后一个
cells.
输出
So this last output is this arrow here,
这个箭头表示这个最后输出
is the last output from the LSTM cells,
LSTM 单元的最后输出
and we're ignoring all these other outputs.
我们将忽略所有这些其他输出
So then these outputs from the LSTM
LSTM 中的这些输出
are just going to a fully connected layer that
将进入完全连接层
only has one unit because we're just
该层级只有 1 个单元
doing this one like sigmoid predictor unit.
因为我们只有一个 Sigmoid 预测器单元
So the activation function is here, tf.sigmoid,
这是激活函数 tf.sigmoid
and this gives us our prediction.
这是我们的预测
So remember that sigmoid is always between 0 and 1,
Sigmoid函数的输出是 0 到 1 之间
so you can treat it as a probability that is true,
你可以将其当做结果为 true 的概率
it's a probability that is positive.
也就是结果为 positive 的概率
Then here we're just using our labels and our predictions
这里 我们使用标签和预测
to calculate the cost with the mean squared error.
计算代价 用均方误差表示
And finally, we have our AdamOptimizer
最后是 AdamOptimizer
that is going to minimize our cost and train the weights.
它将用来减小代价并训练权重
And here I added this little bit to use
这里我添加了一小段代码
as a validation accuracy.
用来计算验证的准确性
So I'm just rounding our predictions,
我对预测四舍五入
because remember predictions are somewhere between 0 and 1.
因为预测在 0 到 1 之间
But we want them to be 0 and 1 so that we can say,
但是我们希望它们为 0 和 1
is it equal to our labels?
这样可以判断是否等于我们的标签
So here I'm just rounding predictions,
这里我对预测四舍五入
so this makes it either 0 or 1, depending on what the value is.
使其等于 0 或 1 具体取决于值为多少
And then I'm going to change the data type,
然后更改数据类型
I'm going to cast it to an int because our labels are ints.
我将其转型为整型 因为标签是整型
So we want these to have the same data types so that we
我们希望它们的数据类型相同
can do this check of equality.
这样才能检测是否相等
Remember that we're passing in a bunch of batches.
我们传入一系列批次
So we have a batch and we're passing in a bunch of reviews
我们有一个批次 我们在每个批次
with each batch.
传入一批影评
So now we actually want to find the mean
现在我们想计算
for all these accuracies.
所有这些准确性的均值
To do that, we're going to use tf.reduce_mean,
为此 我们将使用 tf.reduce_mean
so this just finds the mean of all the predictions,
该函数将计算所有预测的均值
and it's going to give us our accuracy.
并得出准确性
So here, correct prediction is actually
correct_pred 是布尔型
a boolean, that's what the data type comes out of equal.
这是 equal 的返回数据类型
So we actually have to cast this to a float
我们需要将这个转型为浮点型
to get it to work in reduce_mean.
这样才能用于 reduce_mean
So that's what's going on here.
这段代码就是这些作用
Then here is just a function to get batches for us.
这个函数负责获取批次
So you can read this text and read through it,
你可以阅读这段文字并查看代码
but this is pretty typical.
但是代码很典型
So basically I just have two arrays
我有两个数组
x and y and then here I'm just making sure
x 和 y 这里我确保
that every batch is a full batch, so I'm kind of just
每个批次都是完整批次
getting rid of extra data.
我去除了额外数据
And then I'm just looping through each of these arrays
然后循环访问每个数组
and in this case yielding batches.
并输出批次
And finally, this code is the training code.
最后 这段代码是训练代码
So this is a lot of code and it's pretty standard.
代码很长 非常标准
This is really similar to training code
这基本上是我
that I write in every single of these notebooks.
在每个 notebook 中都会写的类似代码
So if you want to kind of like an extra challenge to you,
如果你想挑战下自己
just go ahead and delete this entire cell
可以删了整个代码段
and then try to implement it yourself.
并自己去实现
One way, probably the best way to learn this stuff,
最佳学习方法就是
is to actually type everything yourself, because that's
自己编写所有代码
sort of the deal with tutorials, is that you just
因为这就是教程的特征
read these tutorials and you think you learned it
你阅读了这些教程 以为学会了
but then you try to do it and it turns out
但是当你去尝试的时候
you didn't learn it because you didn't type it in yourself.
实际上并没学会 因为你并没有亲自去写这些代码
So it would probably be a good idea for you
所以最好是
to just delete all this training code and try to implement it
删掉所有这些训练代码
yourself.
自己去实现
And of course, you can copy this to another file
当然了 你可以将这段代码复制到另一个文件中
so you can look at that and see how you're doing.
可以对比看看你的编写效果
And finally, we have testing code down here.
最后 下面的是测试代码
So I will let you build all this, do the exercises,
我将请你编写所有这些 完成练习
and run this code.
并运行这段代码
And if you have problems with this,
如果你遇到了问题
I'm going to have a solution video also and a solution
我将提供解决方案视频和解决方案 notebook
notebook so you can see how I did all this.
你可以看看我是如何完成的
OK, cheers!
加油！